Menu Close

Search

Search for  Search

* Solutions
    * * By Focus Area
        
        * By Institution Type
        
        * Featured Solutions
        * [Enroll360 | Enrollment Management Solution Unlock every recruitment advantage with tailored partnerships for next-generation search, recruitment, and yield](https://eab.com/solutions/enroll360/)
        * [Navigate360 | Higher Ed's Leading CRM Navigate360 is the CRM trusted by 850 schools to recruit, retain, and empower students in college and beyond](https://eab.com/solutions/navigate360/)
        * [Edify | The Higher Education Data Platform Pair powerful data warehousing technology with direct-to-user analytics tools to empower better decision-making across campus](https://eab.com/solutions/edify/)
        * [Strategic Advisory Services | Expert Guidance for Leadership Teams Drive progress on all your institutional priorities with expert guidance and hands-on support from EAB](https://eab.com/solutions/strategic-advisory-services/)
        * [Adult Learner Recruitment | Full-Funnel Grad Enrollment Solution Reach, enroll, and serve graduate, online, and adult learners with next-generation marketing and growth strategies](https://eab.com/solutions/adult-learner-recruitment/)
        * [Virtual Tours | Award-Winning Immersive Tour Experiences Bring your campus story to life with immersive tours that drive student engagement and inquiries](https://eab.com/solutions/virtual-tours/)
* Resources and Insights
    * * Resource Topics
        
        * Resources by Type

            Read about emerging trends and innovative ideas across 8 EAB blogs—covering student success, enrollment, K12, IT, and more.
            
        * 

            Tune in for discussions about the hottest topics in education, featuring higher ed leaders and special guests.
            
* Events
* About Us
* Why EAB

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy
==============

###### Last updated on September 20, 2023

EAB and Our Commitment to Your Privacy
--------------------------------------

**Who Is EAB?** EAB Global, Inc. (together with its subsidiaries and its affiliates, including Cappex.com, LLC d/b/a Appily, “EAB”, “us,” “we,” and “our”) drives transformative change through data-driven insights in five major areas: enrollment; student success; data & analytics; institutional strategy; and diversity, equity, and inclusion (DE&I). We partner with education leaders, practitioners, and staff to accelerate progress and drive results in the most pressing and complex issues facing colleges, universities, community colleges, K-12 school districts, independent schools, and graduate programs in the country. We also partner with more than 450 corporations to provide a collaboration platform among education and corporate leaders to address equity gaps.

**EAB’s Commitment to Privacy.**  EAB is deeply committed to maintaining the privacy and security of personal information we collect or which is provided to us directly by our clients. We value your trust in sharing your personal information with us and are dedicated to protecting your privacy, as further described in this Privacy Policy.

**Updates to this Privacy Policy.** From time to time, this Privacy Policy may be updated to reflect changes to our products and services, the way we operate, or to meet new legal and regulatory requirements. You will find the latest version of this Privacy Policy at [**https://eab.com/privacy-policy**](https://eab.com/privacy-policy).

**Scope of this Privacy Policy**
--------------------------------

This Privacy Policy governs the information collected through EAB.com and all services we provide directly to you, including the EAB Research Forums services. It applies to personal information that can be associated with an identified or identifiable person. This Privacy Policy does not relate to anonymized, aggregated, or de-identified data. Whether you are accessing one or more of our public websites, exploring employment opportunities through our job portal, participating in a research membership forum, or using one of our products via a software application, this Privacy Policy governs our use of personal information for all our products and services that we provide directly to you.  When we collect personal information directly from you in connection with our interactions with you, we are a data controller.

The following privacy notices provide additional information about certain of EAB’s services:

**Scope of your institution’s privacy policies.** If you are an employee, student, prospective student, or other end user of our client, and we are collecting your personal information in connection with the products and services we provide to our clients, we are a data processor. In this case, our use of your personal information is governed by the privacy policy of the institution from which we have received, or on whose behalf we collected or use, your personal information (“your institution”). Our Privacy Policy does not supersede the terms of any agreements between us and your institution, nor does it affect the terms of any agreements between you and your institution, including any prior consent you have provided concerning the use and distribution of your personal information.

Information That We Collect
---------------------------

The type of personal information we collect about you depends upon your relationship with us. Please click on the plus symbol to collapse or expand the relevant section below to learn more. The other sections in our Privacy Policy apply to all our activities.

### Website Visitors and EAB Research Forums Users

EAB maintains websites that are generally accessible by the public.  Our websites provide general information about our company and its products and services.  Our websites also may contain information concerning employment opportunities and provide the opportunity for individuals to submit applications for open roles.  We may do this directly or through third party vendors.

You can generally visit our websites without having to register or otherwise identify yourself. You may need to log in to make use of all the functionalities and be able to communicate with us or other EAB clients. For example, our website allows our clients’ registered users that subscribe to our research forums to access reports and other data.  Our research forums may also provide additional functionality that registered users can access through our website.

We collect personal information in the following manner:

* **Directly from you**: We collect certain personal information directly from you, including your name, email address, institution and role, and account credentials when you register on one or more of our websites. You also may provide personal information to us in connection with your use of the user forums, for example if you attend sessions or events, or if you link your LinkedIn or Twitter account with your EAB Research Forums account, or through the automated virtual assistant and live chat features on our websites.
* **Indirectly from you**: We collect information about your online activities on websites and connected devices over time and across third-party websites, devices, apps and other online features and services for analytics purposes (including the pages you visit and how you access and use our services using cookies and third-party analytics tools (e.g., log files, event data, GPS data, clear gifs and scripts)). This information includes information about the device(s) you use to access the service including unique device identifiers, IP address, operating system, browser, internet service provider, referring/exit pages, clickstream data and cookies. Depending on your device settings, we may also collect information about your geographical location. We may use third-party analytics services, such as Google Analytics and Adobe Analytics to collect this information. The information we obtain may be disclosed to or collected directly by these providers and other relevant third parties who use the information, for example, to evaluate use of EAB’s service or help administer EAB’s services.  To learn more about Google Analytics, please visit [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/).  To learn more about Adobe Analytics, please visit https://www.adobe.com/privacy.html.Learn more about our use of cookies, plugins, analytics or similar tools in our [**Cookie Notice**](https://eab.com/cookie-notice/).
* **Sensitive Information.** We may obtain information relating to your gender or gender identity, and information relating to your health, such as any disabilities, where we are permitted to do so by law or where you give your consent, as required by applicable law.
* **Third Party Integrations, Links and Features.** You may connect third party integrations to your EAB account(s) (e.g., Google SSO), which may ask for certain permissions to send information to your EAB.com account. EAB’s use and transfer of information received from Google APIs will adhere to the [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy). These third parties operate independently from us. The privacy practices of the relevant third parties, including details on the information they may collect about you, are subject to the privacy statements of these parties, which we suggest you review. To the extent any linked online service or third-party feature is not owned or controlled by EAB, we are not responsible for these third parties’ information practices.

### End User of an Institution That Uses Our Products

**Your institution decides how your personal information is used.** We provide nearly all of our products and services to end users of an institution as a “data processor” on behalf of our clients (e.g., colleges, universities, and school districts). This means that the main responsibility for data privacy compliance lies with your institution as a “data controller.” It also means that your institution’s privacy policy governs the use of your personal information (rather than ours). Your institution determines what information we collect through our products and services and how it is used, and we process your information according to your institution’s explicit instructions.

The following section is primarily for informational purposes and describes how your information is generally collected when we provide products and services to you on behalf of a client. How your personal information is used depends on your institution, so you should read your institution’s privacy policy carefully.

We collect personal information in the following manner:

* **Received directly from your institution**: Depending on the products or services that EAB provides to your institution, we may collect the following types of identifiable information:
    * Your name, email address, student ID, account credentials, course enrollment data, grades, and directory information.
    * Application, enrollment and financial aid information.
    * Other information directly from your institution or other third parties related to your enrollment or application status at your institution, or other institutions, or related to your success at your institution.
* **Received directly from you**: Depending on the EAB products and services you use or your institution uses, we may collect the following types of identifiable information:
    * Your name, email address, and similar contact data when you provide or update this information in our products.
    * Application and enrollment information.
    * Your credentials for your institution’s systems account(s) to the extent our products integrate with such systems.
    * Content that you enter directly into our products, including results of surveys or polls, notes and summaries, academic and career preferences.
* **Indirectly from you**: We collect information on your use of our products and services. Depending on the products and services you access or use, we may collect the following data categories indirectly from you:
    * Usage: We collect information about the pages you visit and how you access and use our products using cookies and third-party analytics tools. This information includes information about the device(s) you use to access the websites including unique device identifiers, IP address, operating system, browser and cookies. Depending on your device settings, we may also collect information about your geographical location. Learn more about our use of cookies in our [**Cookie Notice**](https://eab.com/cookie-notice/).

How We Use and Disclose the Information That We Collect
-------------------------------------------------------

We may share the categories of personal information we obtain about you (as described above) with the categories of third parties third parties listed in this section. EAB collects, retains, processes, uses, and transfers your personal information for the following purposes and to the following third parties:

* **To Provide our Services.**  We use personal information that we collect in order to provide our services, including the EAB Research Forums service; verify the identity of users; communicate with users of our services; provide information about briefings, events, professional development sessions, and research collaboration opportunities; manage relationships with users of our services; provide support and troubleshooting services; and improve our services. We process personal information for these purposes because we have a legitimate interest in doing so.
* **Service Providers**: We use service providers to help us provide our products and services to our clients and you or to perform work on our behalf. Where this requires access to personal information, we are responsible for the data privacy practices of the service providers. Our service providers are not allowed to use personal information they access or receive from us for any other purposes than as needed to carry out their work for us. Examples of our service providers include data storage providers, analytics platform providers, survey providers, third party payment providers, print shops.
* **Analytics and Marketing**: We use personal information that we collect in order to analyze use of our services, including the EAB Research Forums service; enhance the services; develop new products or services; and to perform market, trend and statistical research and analysis.  We analyze usage information for marketing purposes and for trends about our visitors’ demographics and use of our websites and services. This analysis is necessary to further our legitimate interest in understanding our users and how they interact with us and our website, improving our website and communicating with you. For more information about our use of third-party analytics tools, please see Section 3 of this Privacy Policy. You can learn more about our use of cookies in our [**Cookie Notice**](https://eab.com/cookie-notice/).
* **Interest-Based or Targeted Advertising.** We may obtain information about your online activities to provide you with advertising about products and services that may be tailored to your interests. This type of advertising is commonly referred to as interest-based advertising or targeted advertising. You may see our ads on other websites because we use third-party ad services. These services track your online activities over time and across third-party websites and apps by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, web server logs, web beacons and other similar technologies. The ad services use this information to show you ads that may be tailored to your individual interests. The ad services may collect information including data about your visits to websites that serve EAB advertisements, such as the pages or ads you view and the actions you take on the websites or apps. This information may be used for purposes of conversion tracking. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts. To learn how to opt out of interest-based or targeted advertising, please visit www.aboutads.info/choices, www.networkadvertising.org/choices/, and http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/. If you are a California resident, please see the EAB California Privacy Notice here for more information about your right to opt out of the “sale” or “sharing” of your personal information in this context.
* **Record Keeping.**  We use personal information that we collect for our internal record keeping purposes, and for accounting, audit and other internal functions.
* **On behalf of your institution**: For end users of institutions that use our products, we use your information on behalf of and under the instruction of your institution, which is the data controller. We share the information that we collect in accordance with our agreement with your institution. Your institution determines how your information is used.
* **Product enhancements and research**: To the extent permitted by applicable law or by our agreement with your institution, we may also use:
    
    * Your personal information to evaluate and improve our products and services to develop new products and services;
    
    * To tailor your experience on our websites; and/or
    
    * De-identified information for research or business purposes like providing similarly-situated institutions a benchmarking data report on completion rates or class size.
* **Client engagement and marketing**: EAB uses your information for client engagement and marketing purposes in limited circumstances, including:
    
    * To manage the client relationship, including for invoicing, notification of product updates and maintenance, and similar purposes.
    
    * To promote EAB’s products and services.
    
    * To share with EAB’s subsidiaries or affiliates. For example, information from a participant in a research webinar may be shared with our advancement affiliate to send services and other promotional communications to you.

We do not disclose personal information about students that we collect through the provision of our educational products and services to third parties for behavioral targeting of advertisements to students.

Our marketing emails will include a link so that you can opt-out of receiving marketing communications from us. You can do this by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link in the email footer.

You can learn more about our use of cookies in our [**Cookie Notice**](https://eab.com/cookie-notice/).

* **Other types of uses and disclosures**: We will also use and share your information to the extent required or appropriate in the following circumstances:
    
    * For EAB Research Forums users, to other users of the EAB Research Forums service.
    
    * To industry associations and other businesses with which EAB co-hosts events, if you chose to participate.
    
    * To comply withlegal or regulatory requirements and to respond to lawful requests, court orders, and legal processes.
    
    * To protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of us, our clients, or third parties, including enforcing contracts or policies or in connection with investigating and preventing fraud.
    
    * To process transactions when you use our services to make a deposit to one of our clients, we will share your payment and transaction data with third party payment processors.
    
    * To carry out operational tasks for legitimate business purposes.
    
    * In the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets (including in the event of a reorganization, dissolution, or liquidation).

Children’s Privacy
------------------

EAB’s products and services are not intended for children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect any information from children. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information upon request. Please contact us at **[\[email protected\]](https://eab.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)** if you believe we have inadvertently collected personal information from a child under 13 without proper consent.

Your Rights and Choices
-----------------------

If you are a California resident, for more information about your privacy rights, please see the EAB Privacy Notice for California Residents [here](https://eab.com/privacy-policy/ccpa-resident-notice/), or the Privacy Notice for California Residents available on our service-specific privacy notices linked above.

**If you are a resident of Colorado, Connecticut, Utah or Virginia****,** you **may** have the right to request:

* that we provide you with access to the personal information collected about you;
* that we provide a copy of your personal information to you in a portable format;
* that we correct or update your personal information that is inaccurate, incomplete or outdated and that you are not otherwise able to update via your profile;
* that we delete your personal information;
* to opt out of the sale of your personal information to third parties; or
* to opt out of the processing of your personal information for purposes of targeted advertising.

You may also have the right to appeal our decision with respect to a request you have submitted [here](https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fprivacyportal.onetrust.com%2Fwebform%2F2d4f8bee-b269-434d-a07f-3b94c6618cb4%2Fdraft%2Fbc55822f-5160-46e9-b1b9-604188a18fce&data=05%7C01%7Ceclinton%40eab.com%7Cdc739344d57a4696954808dae442147d%7Cac1f7d2bc74143f69893d39b22c46953%7C0%7C0%7C638073269700995526%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&sdata=cZg27aN%2BcrKivEVPcki9sJ3oEYZ891wodUgh0RE6%2Bts%3D&reserved=0).

If you wish to exercise any of the rights described above in relation to your personal information, please submit a request to EAB by clicking [here](https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fprivacyportal.onetrust.com%2Fwebform%2F2d4f8bee-b269-434d-a07f-3b94c6618cb4%2Fdraft%2Fb8716d66-85dd-45f4-9c05-a0cf36696f10&data=05%7C01%7Ceclinton%40eab.com%7Cdc739344d57a4696954808dae442147d%7Cac1f7d2bc74143f69893d39b22c46953%7C0%7C0%7C638073269700839283%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&sdata=joOXL8LIUXcH80lHZvSruFODCaI23N0JPTzE9sJi5%2Fo%3D&reserved=0). Prior to fulfilling your request, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity. To submit an opt-out request as an authorized agent on behalf of a consumer, please click [here](https://nam12.safelinks.protection.outlook.com/?url=https%3A%2F%2Fprivacyportal.onetrust.com%2Fwebform%2F2d4f8bee-b269-434d-a07f-3b94c6618cb4%2Fdraft%2Fb8716d66-85dd-45f4-9c05-a0cf36696f10&data=05%7C01%7Ceclinton%40eab.com%7Cdc739344d57a4696954808dae442147d%7Cac1f7d2bc74143f69893d39b22c46953%7C0%7C0%7C638073269700839283%7CUnknown%7CTWFpbGZsb3d8eyJWIjoiMC4wLjAwMDAiLCJQIjoiV2luMzIiLCJBTiI6Ik1haWwiLCJXVCI6Mn0%3D%7C3000%7C%7C%7C&sdata=joOXL8LIUXcH80lHZvSruFODCaI23N0JPTzE9sJi5%2Fo%3D&reserved=0).

To the extent permitted by applicable law, we may charge a reasonable fee to comply with your request. If you choose to exercise any of these rights, you have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment by us.

Security
--------

We employ a variety of physical, administrative, and technological safeguards designed to protect personal information against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access or disclosure.

Specific Regional & Country Information
---------------------------------------

### European Union

EAB is not established in the European Union (“EU”) or the United Kingdom (“UK”); however, in certain limited circumstances, we may be subject to the General Data Protection Regulation or the Data Protection Act of 2018 (collectively, “GDPR”).

EAB’s Privacy Notice for individuals in the EU and UK can be found [here](http://privacy.eab.com/GDPR).

### California

If you are a California resident and are an end user of EAB.com or EAB Research Forums, please see the EAB California Privacy Notice [here](http://privacy.eab.com/eabcom-CA).

If you are a California resident and are an end user of the YouVisit Virtual Tour Program, Cappex. please see the California Privacy Notice linked to the applicable Privacy Notice.

If you are a job applicant to EAB, please see the California Job Applicant Privacy Notice [here](http://privacy.eab.com/employee-CA).

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data privacy practices, contact us at **[\[email protected\]](https://eab.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)** or write to us at the following address.

EAB Global, Inc.  
Attn: General Counsel  
2445 M Street, NW  
Washington, DC 20037

* ### Solutions by Focus Area
    
* ### Solutions by Institution Type

* ### Why EAB
    
* ### Resources and Insights

* ### Events
    
* ### About Us

* ### Communications

Copyright © 2024 EAB

### It appears you already have an account registered with us.  
Please login below or reset your password.

Login

Email 

Password 

 Remember me

Reset Password Form

Email 

Reset Password Cancel
